<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Han Wuguang</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Han Wuguang</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- 0.145.0</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>I&#39;ve got my AWS certifications 😆</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/2025-03-26_aws-certification/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/2025-03-26_aws-certification/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;m overjoyed that I&amp;rsquo;ve obtained the Amazon Web Services (AWS) DevOps Professional, Solutions Architect Professional and Security Specialty certifications.
I did the certifications because I wanted to validate my skills after working on projects on AWS for a number of years.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I passed the exams in a single attempt within a month and would like to share some tips:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Lots of hands-on experience - Throughout the course of my work, I had to use a broad range of AWS services to deliver my projects. This helped me understand each service well and how various services work together (i.e. the architectural aspect). Such knowledge simply can&amp;rsquo;t be gleaned from rote memorization of documentation. You&amp;rsquo;ve got to get your hands dirty and try to build a system.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/about/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;about-me&#34;&gt;About Me&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;m a combination of software architect, developer and systems engineer.
Throughout my career of more than 15 years, I&amp;rsquo;ve designed software systems, written code in various programming languages and maintained IT infrastructures.
Like everyone else, I started with basic progamming skills that I learnt in school.
With an inquisitive mind and a keen interest in technology, I started working on personal projects to help me develop my skills.
This blog serves as journal of my learning journey.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
